designconnected.com 2013-05-07

# Privacy policy

**Your privacy is important for us.**

**What personal data we collect**

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

When you register an account, purchase or download a product or participate in an online survey, we may collect information, including your name, mailing address, email address, phone number and other information you may be asked to provide.  
It’s important to know that we do not store on file your credit card details you provide when you make a purchase on designconnected.com. 

**How we process your personal data**

The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on the latest 3d models, announcements and events. It’s helping us to improve our services and content. If you don’t want to receive any emails from us, you can opt out anytime by updating your account preferences.

We also use your personal data to develop new products and services or for internal data analysis and research.

**Use of non-personal data**

We may also collect non-personal data which does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may use and/or disclose non-personal data for any purpose.

**Cookies**

We may use “cookies” to better understand our website visitor’s behavior or to remember personal information when you use our website to offer you better and more personal experience.  
We treat all data collected by “cookies” as personal for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

**Protection**

Designconnected online services use Geotrust certified Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal data is collected.   
In addition, designconnected.com website is daily monitored and protected by McAfee Secure service for possible personal information access, links to dangerous sites, phishing, and other online dangers: https://www.mcafeesecure.com/RatingVerify?ref=www.designconnected.com.

**Disclosure to third parties**

We shall not reveal any personal data and shall not provide or transfer the collected personal data to third parties – state or municipal authorities, companies, natural persons and others, except in the following cases: 

  * you have expressed your explicit consent during or after the registration process;
  * the personal data is duly requested by competent authorities in compliance with the applicable law; or
  * in other provided for by the applicable law.
